# **SAKA MUSA ABIOLA**

#### FULL-STACK ENGINEER

+2349018500242, +2349167695673

satifiedms@gmail.com

No. 12, Asubiojo Compound, New Gbagi Market, Ibadan, Oyo State satifi

satifiedms.github.io

### **PROFILE**

A tech savvy and trained programmer with fierce interest in OOP programming languages majorly C++, Java and PHP. Currently exploring the web, building applications that will make humans interaction with the realm a more interesting experience. I believe man are not meant to work alone, and to go far in life, we all need a company.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### Edu-Consults Ibadan

CBT Instructor | 2013 - 2015

 Teaching of general computer knowledge and preparation of students for Computer-Based UTME Examination

#### **Opera News Hub**

Content Creator | 2020 - 2021

Gathering and publication of news contents, articles and listicles

#### UNDERTAKEN PROJECTS

- Implementation Of EMR System For FUT Minna Health Center
  - Undergraduate Final Year Project | 2023
- Implementation of Backend for financeflow.com.ng

Freelance Project | 2023

#### **EDUCATION**

## Federal University Of Technology Minna, Niger State

Bachelor of Technology in Computer Science 2017 – 2023

### Urban Day Grammar School Ibadan, Oyo State

2005 - 2011

# **Ibadan District Community School Ibadan, Oyo State**

1998-2005

#### SKILLS

- Full-stack web development
- · Excellent PHP script writing
- Fluency in Laravel framework
- Efficiency in MySQL DBMS
- Excellent React library usageJavaScript (JQuery) scripting
- Proficiency in CSS (Bootstrap) writing
- Excellent communication skill
- · Excellent technical writing

#### CERTIFICATIONS

- · Desktop Publishing Certification
- Computer Repair and Maintenance Certification